

ALPER TOLGA ERBEK

Summary

Phone: +905453994936

Address: Dumlupinar neigh. Kilic street. Nu:4/10, Kadikoy/Istanbul
Website: http://linkedin.com/in/alper-tolga-erbek-57b7ab1ab

Email: alpertolgaerbek@gmail.com

To whom it may concern, I am an electric and electronic engineer candidate at Marmara University, last grade. I have internship experience at three different firm at Turkey. I used drawing programs such as AutoCAD and MATLAB Simulink while working at these firms.

EXPERIENCE

Tubitak 04.10.2021 - 21.01.2022

Intern

I have been working on renewable energy such as solar energy, photovoltaic panels.

Gecem Lighting 11.08.2021 - 30.09.2021

Intern

I did 36 days internship about lighting technologies. I worked on quality control of lighting products.

Alp Construction Engineering, Natural Gas

20.08.2020 - 26.09.2020

Intern

I worked on electric projects which created using AutoCAD.

EDUCATION

Marmara University 2018-2022

Electric and Electronic Engineering

Last grade, GPA is 77.5/100.

Carsamba High School 2013-2017

Science

GPA is 88/100.

SKILLS

AutoCAD

MATLAB

C Programming Language

All MS Office Programs

VOLUNTEERING

Marmara University Student Club

2020

Building Playground for Children

I collected some money through donations and our club bought some playground stuffs for children who stay at prison with their parents.

LANGUAGES

English (Intermediate)

CERTIFICATIONS

Diction Course Certificate

Baskent Communication Course

I attended to diction course and deserve a certificate.

RECOMMENDATIONS

İlhan Buyurucu

Electric and Electronic Engineer at Gecem Lighting

Telephone Number: +905511195607

İbrahim Demir

Electric and Electronic Engineer at Alp Structure

Telephone Number: +905435519652

Seval Meriç

Assoc. Prof. Dr at Tubitak

Telephone Number: +902626795000 Email Address: seval.meric@tubitak.gov.tr

HOBBIES

Walking

Football Referee 2021-Present

I am amateur football leagues referee at Istanbul.

Swimming

2019